James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1990-2010; 2
  - General, 1996-2010; 1
    - Redistricting (2 of 5), 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Redistricting (3 of 5), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting (4 of 5), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting (5 of 5), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Religious Liberty, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Restoration, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Retirement, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Re-zoning, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rural Affairs, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Same-Sex Marriage, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Scholarships, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Sexual Assault, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Small Business, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Snakes, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Solar Energy, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - State Employees, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Student Letters, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Sunset Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Sunset Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Taxes (1 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Taxes (2 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Taxes, 2003-2006 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Telephones, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Texas Commission on Environmental Quality, 2005-2010 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Texas Constitution, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Texas Education Association, Textbooks, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Texas Lottery, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Texas Lottery, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Texas Poison Center, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Texas Tomorrow Fund, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Thank Yous (1 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Thank Yous (2 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Tort Reform, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, 1997-2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Vehicles, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Veterans’ Affairs, 1998-2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Video Lottery Terminals, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Voting, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Water, 1997-2006 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Welfare, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Workforce Development, 1997-2004 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Worker’s Compensation, 1996-2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Youth, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - McLennan County, 1990-2001; 2
    - General, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - General, 1996 January-February (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - General, 1997 January (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - General, 1997 June (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - General, 1997 July (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - General, 1997 August (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - General, 1997 December (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - General, 1998 January (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - General, 1998 December (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - General, 1999 January (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - General (1 of 2), 1999 February (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 2), 1999 February (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - General, 1999 March (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - General, 1999 April (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - General, 1999 May (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - General, 1999 June (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - General, 1999 August (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - General, 1999 September (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - General, 1999 November (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - General, 2000 March (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - General, 2000 June (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - General, 2000 November (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - General, 2001 January (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - General, 2001 July (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - General, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Members, 1995-2003; 3
    - General, 1995 September (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - General, 1997 January (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - General, 1997 February (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - General, 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - General, 1997 April (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - General, 1997 May (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - General, 1997 June (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - General, 1997 July (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - General, 1997 August (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - General, 1997 September (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - General, 1997 November (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - General, 1997 December (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - General, 1998 February (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - General, 1998 March (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - General, 1998 April (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - General, 1998 August (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - General, 1998 October (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - General, 1998 November (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - General, 1998 December (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - General, 1999 January (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - General, 1999 February (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - General, 1999 March (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - General, 1999 April (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - General, 1999 May (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General, 1999 June (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - General, 1999 July (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - General, 1999 August (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - General, 1999 September (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - General, 1999 October (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - General, 1999 November (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - General, 1999 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - General, 2000 January (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - General, 2000 March (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - General, 2000 April (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - General, 2000 June (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - General, 2000 August (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - General, 2000 September (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - General, 2000 November (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - General, 2000 December (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - General, 2001 June (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - General, 2001 October (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - General, 2001 November (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - General, 2002 January (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - General, 2002 April (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - General, 2002 May (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - General, 2002 June (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - General, 2002 July (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - General, 2003 April (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - General, 2003 June (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - General, 2003 July (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - General, 2003 August (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - General, 2003 October (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - General, 2003 November (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - General, 2003 December (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - General, 2004 June (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - General, 2004 December (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - General, 2005 January (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - General, 2005 April (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - General, 2005 May (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - General, 2005 August (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - General, 2005 September (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - General, 2005 December (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - General, 2006 January (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - General, 2006 February (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - General, 2006 March (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - General, 2006 April (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - General, 2006 June (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - General, 2006 December (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - General, 2007 September (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - General, 2008 April (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - General, 2008 September (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - General, 2008 November (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - General, 2009 March (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - General, 2009 July (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - General, undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Redistricting, 2003 April (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Redistricting, 2003 May (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Redistricting, 2003 October (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Redistricting, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Constituents, 1993-2011; 3
  This series holds constituent material from the 57th District. It contains the subseries: Cities and Counties, Phone Logs, Questionnaires, Reading Files, Speeches, and Thank Yous. Questionnaires consists of education funding questionnaires from 2005. A few topics among the Speeches are the Bosque River, Education, Memorial Day, and physical activity for children. With the exception of Cities and Counties and Speeches, the other subseries are arranged chronologically. This series is in good condition.
  - Cities and Counties, 1993-2001; 1
    - Bellmead, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Bellmead, La Vega ISD, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Crawford, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Fire Departments, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Hallsburg, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lacy Lakeview, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Mart, 1997-2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - McGregor, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - McLennan County, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Moody, 1993-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Riesel, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - West, 1997-2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Waco (1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Waco (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Phone Logs, 1997-2010; 2
    - General (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - General (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - General (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - General (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - General (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 4), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 4), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General (3 of 4), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - General (4 of 4), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 4), 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 4), 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - General (3 of 4), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - General (4 of 4), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - General (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - General (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - General (1 of 3), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires, 2005; 3
    - Education Funding (1 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Education Funding (2 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Education Funding (3 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Education Funding (4 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Education Funding (5 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Education Funding (6 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Education Funding (7 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Education Funding (8 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Education Funding (9 of 17), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Education Funding (10 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Education Funding (11 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Education Funding (12 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Education Funding (13 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Education Funding (14 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Education Funding (15 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Education Funding (16 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Education Funding (17 of 17), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Reading Files, 1997-2000; 4
    - General, 1997 January (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - General, 1997 February (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - General (1 of 2), 1997 March (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - General (2 of 2), 1997 March (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - General, 1997 April-May (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - General (1 of 3), 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 2), 1997 May (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 2), 1997 May (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - General, 1997 June-December (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - General, 1998 September-October (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - General, 1999 January (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - General (1 of 2), 1999 February (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - General (2 of 2), 1999 February (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1999 March (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1999 March (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 2), 1999 April (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 2), 1999 April (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 2), 1999 May (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 2), 1999 May (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - General, 1999 August (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - General, 1999 September-October (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - General, 1999 October (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - General, 1999 November (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - General, 1999 December (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - General, 2000 January (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - General, 2000 February (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - General, 2000 March (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - General, 2000 April (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - General, 2000 May (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, 1997-2003; 5
    - Bosque River, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Changes in the Past Century, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Christmas, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Education, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Education, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Mae Jackson, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Memorial Day, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Nurse Oncology Education Program, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Parent-Teacher Association, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Physical Activity for Children, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Texas Democratic Women, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - 75th Session, c. 1997 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Thank Yous, 1997-2006; 6
    - General, 1997-2006 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  The Legislative series contains material from the 75th through 81st Legislative sessions, 1996-2010, the length of Dunnam’s service as a member of the Texas House of Representatives. It contains the subseries: General, 75th Session, 76th Session, 77th Session, 78th Session, 79th Session, 80th Session, 81st Session, Committees, Democratic Caucus, Memos, and Topical. The subseries General through 81st Session include some or all of the following sub-subseries: General, Correspondence, House Bills, Senate Bills, Joint Resolutions, Commemoratives and Commendations, and Topical. The subseries Committees consists of numerous sub-subseries representing committees Dunnam was a member of, chaired, or for which he had files. Democratic Caucus contains materials related to Dunnam’s leadership of the House Democratic Caucus from 2003-2011. Memos are arranged chronologically and topically within the General sub-subseries and by “Monday Memos" from 2003. The Topical subseries contains the sub-subseries: Ardmore (Killer Ds), Bosque River, Charter Schools, Redistricting, School Finance, Supreme Court of Texas, Texas Youth Commission, and tort reform. The Legislative series is in good condition.
  - General, 1996-2010, undated; 1
    - House Bills, 1997-2001, undated; 1
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Agriculture Rural Affairs, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Banking, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Consumers Business Interests, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Crime, Corrections Guns, Law Enforcement, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Economic Development/ Transportation, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Education, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Ethics, Elections Camp Finance, Pay, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Environment, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Gays/Lesbians, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Health, Human Services, Safety, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Intergovernmental Relations, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Juvenile Justice and Family Issues, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Labor, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Minorities, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Revenue and Spending, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Dunnam House Floor Votes, Women, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - HB 6/SB 104, Occupations Code, Amendments, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - HB 761, Ethics And Accountability In State Government, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Potential Legislation, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Commemoratives and Commendations, undated; 2
      - HR, Steve and Mary Hurtado 50th Wedding Anniversary, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Topical, 1996-2010, undated; 3
      - Animal Emergency Law, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Coloring Books, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Election, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Got Quorum? T-Shirt, undated (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 2)
      - Hazardous Waste, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Questionnaires, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Sunset Commission Review of Texas Department of Insurance, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Transportation Subcommittee on Toll Roads Information, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Waters of Texas Bottle, 2003 March 3 (Box 81 OVZ, Folder 3)
      - Voting Record, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 75th Session, 1996-2002; 2
    - General, 1997-2002; 1
      - Coalition for Public Schools Thank You Letter, 1997 May 16 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Dunnam Attendance, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Dunnam’s House and Senate Bills Summary, 1997 June 5 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Dunnam Voting History, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - House Bills, HB1 Conference Committee Report Summary, 1997 May (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - House Research Organization Interim News, 1997 Dec (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - House Rules Reform, 1997 Jan (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Interim Charges, House Committee on Agriculture and Livestock, 1997 Sept (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Memorial Day Legislation Massacre Speech, 1997 May 27 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Opening Day, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Receipts, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Summary of Major Issues, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - 75th-77th Session Attendance and Voting Record, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - House Bills, 1997, undated; 2
      - Bills Introduced by Dunnam, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - HB 311, Prosecution of Offenses Involving Firearms or Prohibited Weapons, Committee Report, 1997 May 29 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - HB 318, School Vouchers, General, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - HB 318, Amendments, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - HB 318, Record Vote, 1997 May 6 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - HB 485, Out-of-State Inmates, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - HB 515, Waiver of a Trial by Jury, General, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - HB 515, Amendment Request, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - HB 515, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - HB 515, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - HB 515, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - HB 515, State of Texas v. Chaouachi, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - HB 749, Discharge of Criminal Proceedings because of Delay in Presentment of Information or Indictment, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - HB 768, Employee Discrimination and Workers Compensation, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - HB 768, Discrimination Against an Employee Based on Claim for Workers’ Compensation Benefits, Committee Report, 1997 May 28 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - HB 1113, Texas Municipal Retirement System, Amendment, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - HB 1188, Home Equity Lending, Amendments, circa 1997 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - HB 1202, Premises Liability, Amendments, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - HB 1202, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - HB 1425, Interlocutory Appeal of Court Orders Relating To Arbitration, General, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - HB 1425, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - HB 1425, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - HB 1425, Fiscal Note, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - HB 1425, Relevant Cases, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - HB 1425, Talking Point, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - HB 2150, Repeal of Exemption of Professional Services from Liability, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - HB 2254, Census and District Maps, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - HB 2517, General, Public Post-Secondary Education, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - HB 2517, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - HB 2517, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - HB 2517, Committee Substitute, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - HB 2517, Fiscal Note, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - HB 2518, Bill Analysis, State Aircraft Transfer to Public Post- Secondary Schools, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - HB 2518, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - HB 2158, Committee, Amendment, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - HB 2518, Fiscal Note, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - HB 2811, Appeal from Entry of a Protective Order, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - HB 2811, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - HB 2811, Committee Substitute, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - HB 2811, Court of Appeals, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - HB 2811, Fiscal Note, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - HB 3034, General, Reimbursement to Municipalities of Certain Lottery Revenue, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - HB 3034, Deductions from Compensation Paid to Lottery Sales Agents, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - HB 3081, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - HB 3081, Bill Text, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - HB 3081, Amendment, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - HB 3081, Committee Substitute, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - HB 3081, Fiscal Note, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - HB 3081, Talking Points, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Senate Bills, 1997; 3
      - SB 185, Prosecution Of Certain Sexual Assaults Committed Against Children, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - SB 271, Amendments, circa 1997 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - SB 271, Alcoholic Beverage Distribution, Bill Analysis, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - SB 1425, Appeal of Court Orders and Judgments Relating to Arbitration, Substitute, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - SB 1577, Transfer of TSTC Abilene to Cisco Junior College, Point of Order, circa 1997 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Joint Resolutions, 1997; 4
      - HJR 73, Maintenance Costs for Private Roads, Amendments, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - HJR 73, Record Vote, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Commemoratives and Commendations, 1996-1997; 5
      - HCR 185, City Of West, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - HR 117, Newman, Cody, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - HR 406, Robinson High School Band, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - HR 978, Upton, Nancy, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Resolution Requests, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Topical, 1996-1997; 6
      - Associations, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Automobile Insurance, 1997 February-March (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Boll Weevils, 1997 April-May (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Checkpoint and Open Container Laws, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Chiropractic Education, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Cock Fighting, 1997 February-March (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Community Youth Development Program, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Driving Safety, 1997 January-April (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Electric Utility, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Environmental, General, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Environmental Issues, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Faculty Teaching Loads, c. 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)